<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lieu de Mémoire on Our Journey - Gallery</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lieu de Mémoire on Our Journey - Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>id-id</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>📂 Encrypted Correspondance</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notre-histoire/encrypted-correspondance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notre-histoire/encrypted-correspondance/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/notre-histoire/encrypted-correspondance/e-2_hu_aa9a32d151ec51c0.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/notre-histoire/encrypted-correspondance/e-2_hu_aa9a32d151ec51c0.jpg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;This archive contains the duality of our existence. On one side, the raw, unfiltered messages of two souls finding home. On the other, the intercepted threats and sasaeng logs that were silenced before they could reach the light.

_Current Encryption Status: AES-256 Bit. Access restricted to C &amp; M only._
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
    <item>
      <title>Âmes Sœurs</title>
      <link>https://example.org/ames-soeurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/ames-soeurs/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/ames-soeurs/5_hu_c34f4d8b22ac8381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/ames-soeurs/5_hu_c34f4d8b22ac8381.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The strobe lights are supposed to make me feel alive, but tonight, everything feels dull. I&#39;m standing in the center of the podium, draped in a heavy winter collection, letting dozens of photographers capture the best angles of my jawline. I&#39;m doing my job. Being the perfect, cold, and untouchable statue. But my eyes keep drifting to the dark corner behind the rows of massive cables.

There sits a man who isn&#39;t wearing an expensive suit. Loui, is just in a black shirt with sleeves rolled to his elbows, his eyes fixed on a laptop screen displaying complex encryption graphs. He&#39;s here as the head of cybersecurity for the event. Ensuring there are no data leaks or broadcast signal hacks.

He hasn&#39;t looked up at me once. Everyone in this room is worshipping me, but him... it&#39;s as if he&#39;s intentionally ignoring my existence.

_Bastard._

I shift my pose, turning my face exactly in his direction, hoping he realizes I&#39;m staring at him through countless camera lenses. I want him to see how beautiful I look tonight. I want him to feel possessive because everyone else wants me.

Suddenly, the tiny earpiece I wear for stage cues crackles. It&#39;s not the manager&#39;s voice I hear, but a deep, familiar rumble.

&#34;Chin down, Mowi. You&#39;re losing focus,&#34; Loui&#39;s voice cuts into my frequency, low and sharp. &#34;Stop looking at me and finish your job. If you miss another step, I&#39;ll kill every light in this building and drag you home before the show is over.&#34;

My heart races. He was watching me through the security cameras, not with his own eyes. He sees me through a screen, as part of the system he controls. I tilt my chin down slightly, a faint smile that shouldn&#39;t be there touching my lips. The photographer in front of me looks ecstatic, thinking I just gave him a &#34;million-dollar&#34; expression. They don&#39;t know that I&#39;m just obeying the command in my ear. As it turns out, being the center of the world&#39;s attention is nothing compared to being the only &#34;bug&#34; Loui bothers to fix on his screen.

*_— Devotedly yours, Myoui Ronmura._*
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
    <item>
      <title>📂 Digital Evidence</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notre-histoire/digital-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notre-histoire/digital-evidence/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/notre-histoire/digital-evidence/evidence5_hu_f44aa32e9cc7e323.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/notre-histoire/digital-evidence/evidence5_hu_f44aa32e9cc7e323.jpg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Freedom is rarely handed over with a smile; it must be extracted with surgical precision. They thought they owned every breath Myoui took, every smile he gave to the camera, and every second of his waking life. They were wrong.

This folder contains the tactical weaponry that finally severed the parasitic bond between a star and his agency. It is a history of corporate greed met with a hacker&#39;s cold, calculating justice. From the meticulously gathered dossiers of internal tax embezzlement to the recorded logs of management malpractice, these files are the leverage that turned the hunters into the hunted.

_Legal Weight: Absolute. This data remains the ultimate ultimatum._
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
    <item>
      <title>📂 Clandestine Memories</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notre-histoire/clandestine-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notre-histoire/clandestine-memories/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/notre-histoire/clandestine-memories/memories1_hu_2aa8bd97b5639063.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/notre-histoire/clandestine-memories/memories1_hu_2aa8bd97b5639063.jpg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The world gets the pose, the expensive lighting, and the manufactured facade of a perfect model. They see the version of Myoui that has been edited, filtered, and sold for profit. But here, lies the &#39;unreleased cut&#39;. The moments that were never meant for the cameras or the magazine covers. This is the reality of a life lived behind closed curtains, where the only audience that matters is the one person holding the lens.

_Visual Status: Archived for private viewing. Not for public distribution._
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour Toujours</title>
      <link>https://example.org/pour-toujours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/pour-toujours/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/pour-toujours/1_hu_57924416dc5597d5.jpeg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/pour-toujours/1_hu_57924416dc5597d5.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;My monitor displays thousands of lines of code that I&#39;m supposed to finish tonight. But honestly, my concentration broke half an hour ago when I heard the key turn in the front door.

It&#39;s Myoui.

I don&#39;t turn around, intentionally staying focused on the screen so he doesn&#39;t know I&#39;ve actually been waiting for him. Not long after, I feel arms wrap around my neck from behind. His floral perfume. A sharp contrast to my room that smells only of coffee, instantly fills my senses.

&#34;Not done yet?&#34; he whispers, resting his chin on my shoulder. His voice sounds tired, but soft.

&#34;Almost, Sayang. There&#39;s one stubborn bug I&#39;ve been chasing,&#34; I reply, trying to stay cool even though I can barely think straight with him leaning against me like this.

Myoui doesn&#39;t protest. He doesn&#39;t ask me to shut down the laptop. Instead, he pulls an empty chair next to mine, sits down, and takes my right hand off the mouse to hold it. He starts telling me little things that happened at the shoot. About the catering being good, or a funny photographer.

I keep looking at the screen, but my left hand is just typing gibberish now because I&#39;d rather listen to his voice.

&#34;Are you even listening?&#34; he asks, poking my nose.

I finally rotate my chair, looking at him fully. He looks incredibly beautiful even with his makeup slightly faded. I brush a stray hair out of his eyes, then pull him closer, near enough that our knees touch.

&#34;I&#39;m listening. To everything,&#34; I say softly. I take off my glasses, a sign that I&#39;m officially giving up on work for the night. &#34;After all, no matter how advanced the system I&#39;m building is, nothing catches my attention quite like you when you&#39;re talking like this.&#34;

Myoui smiles, the kind of genuine smile he never gives to the cameras. He leans his head on my shoulder, playing with my fingers.

&#34;Don&#39;t push yourself too hard. You&#39;ll get sick,&#34; he says caringly.

I just chuckle softly and kiss the top of his head. &#34;I know, I know. I&#39;m done after this. Should we just order some food?&#34;

To the world, I might be the programmer who only cares about numbers and logic. But to Myoui, I&#39;m just his Ludwig, the night owl who always has time to listen to his stories, no matter how trivial they are.

_*Faithfully yours, Calder Ludwig Maximilian.*_
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
    <item>
      <title>La Vie En Rose</title>
      <link>https://example.org/la-vie-en-rose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/la-vie-en-rose/</guid>
        <media:content url="https://example.org/la-vie-en-rose/ginghamcheck_hu_b0792bb3b6021b43.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
        <description>
          &lt;img src=&quot;https://example.org/la-vie-en-rose/ginghamcheck_hu_b0792bb3b6021b43.jpg&quot; /&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The pounding on the apartment door was loud and impatient. &#34;Myoui! Open up! We need to talk about those photos before the agency terminates your contract!&#34; the manager&#39;s voice came through, muffled but sharp with anger.

Inside, Myoui flinched. He stood in the middle of the room, face pale, his eyes darting between the door and Ludwig. His fear of the outside world was still very real.

&#34;Loui, he&#39;s there. He&#39;s going to take me away,&#34; Myoui whispered, panicked.

Ludwig slowly pushed his chair back from the desk. He didn&#39;t look bothered at all. Instead of getting up to open the door, he simply looked at Myoui and patted his lap with a slow, absolute gesture. &#34;Come here,&#34; Ludwig commanded. His voice was low and calm, a stark contrast to the noise outside.

Without a word, Myoui approached. He sat on Ludwig&#39;s lap, wrapping his arms around the man&#39;s neck as if Ludwig were the only shield in a collapsing world. Ludwig wrapped one arm around Myoui&#39;s waist, pulling him closer until Myoui could feel his steady heartbeat.

&#34;Stay here. Don&#39;t make a sound,&#34; Ludwig murmured into Myoui&#39;s ear.

Ludwig reached for his phone, pressing a button linked to the apartment&#39;s intercom system. His voice echoed directly into the hallway, cold and sharp as a blade.

&#34;Leave this floor in ten seconds, or I will leak your agency&#39;s internal logs regarding last year&#39;s tax embezzlement to the public.&#34; Ludwig said, getting straight to the point. An immediate silence followed outside. The pounding stopped.

&#34;Who is this?! Where is Myoui?!&#34; the manager shouted, his voice now trembling.

&#34;Myoui isn&#39;t available. He&#39;s busy being mine,&#34; Ludwig answered with a tone that was almost bored. &#34;Eight seconds left, and it&#39;ll be your career that burns, not his. Choose.&#34;

It only took three seconds to hear hurried footsteps retreating from the door. Ludwig cut the intercom, then turned his focus back to Myoui, who was still shaking in his lap. He rubbed Myoui&#39;s back gently. A rare gesture that finally allowed Myoui to let out a breath of relief.

&#34;See? He&#39;s gone,&#34; Ludwig whispered, kissing Myoui&#39;s temple. &#34;No agency, no manager, no fans. Just you here, in my lap. Now, stay quiet and let me finish my work.&#34;

Myoui hid his face in the crook of Ludwig&#39;s neck, feeling so small yet so incredibly safe. He didn&#39;t care about his million-dollar contracts anymore. Here, in this spot, he finally had an owner who would never let him go.

_One captures the eyes of millions, the other captures the heart of the only one who matters._
*_— Faithfully, Calder &amp; Myoui._*
&lt;/p&gt;
        </description></item>
  </channel>
</rss>